{
    "subject": "resource/D\u00e9j\u00e0_Vu_(Crosby,_Stills,_Nash_&_Young_album)",
    "predicate": "property/released",
    "object": "1970-03-11",
    "human_readable": "D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu, the album by Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young, was released on March 11, 1970.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9797039031982422,
            "question": "What year did Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young release the album 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9463023543357849,
            "question": "Name an album released by Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8718540072441101,
            "question": "When was the album 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8630143404006958,
            "question": "What is the title of the album released on March 11th, 1970?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8524726629257202,
            "question": "What is the name of the album released on March 11, 1970?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8427532911300659,
            "question": "Who performed the album 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7746492028236389,
            "question": "Which musical group is known for the album 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.75709068775177,
            "question": "In what month was the album 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6497870683670044,
            "question": "Is 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu' a famous album in musical history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5425203442573547,
            "question": "March 11th, 1970 marks a significant event in music history. What happened on that day?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu, the album by Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young, was released on March 11, 1970.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1158_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu' a famous album in musical history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1158_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what month was the album 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1158_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which musical group is known for the album 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1158_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1158_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references that confirm the release date of the album D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu by Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young as March 11, 1970."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}